[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does lacrimation mean?", "correct_answer": "Shedding Tears", "incorrect_answers": ["Psychosis", "Addiction", "Dilation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This nut is also a source of folic acid, which diminishes the risk of birth defects and heart diseases. It is often combined with chocolate.", "correct_answer": "Hazelnut", "incorrect_answers": ["Peanut", "Chestnut", "Walnut"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first successful experiment in which a cloned animal embryo reached an adult state, was carried out in what year?", "correct_answer": "1952", "incorrect_answers": ["1907", "1973", "1926"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which top bridge player from India stimulated the development of bridge during the 60s and 70s?", "correct_answer": "Zia Maywood", "incorrect_answers": ["Ghandhi", "Eric Jaggie", "Ria Aymore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Sweet Home Alabama, what problem does the character Malanie Smooter encounter, which prevents her from marrying her fiance Andrew Hennings?", "correct_answer": "She is still married to Jake.", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrews mother wants him to wait.", "It rains on the wedding day.", "Her parents will not give their approval."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these came first?", "correct_answer": "Knotts Berry Farm", "incorrect_answers": ["Busch Gardens", "Freedomland", "Disneyland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sylvester Stallone was born on 6 July 1946 in New York City. He is often referred as Sly- his nickname, which comes from Sylvester. Do you know what his middle name is?", "correct_answer": "Enzio", "incorrect_answers": ["Alois", "Gerald", "Graham"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2004  Dennis Quaid / Sela Ward movie The Day After Tomorrow, books are burned in order to avoid freezing. Why were some characters in the movie angry?", "correct_answer": "They did not burn the furniture.", "incorrect_answers": ["They only burned religious books.", "They burned the encyclopedias first.", "They burned the oldest books first."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a moirologist?", "correct_answer": "Someone paid to mourn at a funeral", "incorrect_answers": ["A well-dressed woman", "A stutterer or stammerer", "A trademark used as a generic term"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these activities can cause permanent damage to the eyes?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Reading in poor light", "Prolonged reading", "Reading small print"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What common expression is used to refer to beer to point out its excellent nutritional properties?", "correct_answer": "Liquid bread", "incorrect_answers": ["Food in a mug", "Golden elixir", "Fizzy tea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the cause of the Malaysia Airlines Flight 653 crash on 4 December 1977?", "correct_answer": "Hijacking", "incorrect_answers": ["Storm", "All of these", "Engine malfunction"]}]